

LEADERSHIP SKILLS

Organized planner
Creative problem-solver
Passionate listener
Empatic motivator
Engaging speaker
Resilient
Initiative taker
Creative spirit
Reliable and professional
Time management
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated

REMOTE TOOLS

- Slack
- Google Drive
- Zoom
- Trello
- Coggle
- Toggl
- Zendesk
- Connecteam
- VSCode
- Sandbox
- Github
- Netlify

MARIËTTE EVERITZ

ABOUT ME

I am a motivated, passionate Customer Server with over 5 years of experience in Customer Support in international, non-profit and profit, educational and creative industries. Interested in joining multicultural organizations where I can apply my knowledge and skills for continuous improvement and share the same values.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

MARKETING - CONTENT SITE MANAGER

Paynovate | August 2021 - Now

- Improving and investigating customer contentment by taking note and necessary action in customer experiences.
- Providing documentation/strategies for colleagues to solve problems of customers and create positive outcome.

FIRST LINER SUPPORT AGENT

Loyaltek | February 2020 - Now

- Provide problemsolving solutions & support to hosts via e-mail and phone.
- Make and solve tickets for the second liners.
- Help improve the remote department of the company (improve communication, documents, employee satisfaction.

Evaluate customer, colleague and own experiences to create better strategies and service.

OPERATIONS

Paynovate | August 2020 - December 2021

- Thoroughly check contracts: company validities, shareholders, given information and perform background checks.
- Migration validation
- Providing documentation and coach/training of (new) colleagues to create better strategies and service.

TELEMARKETING CUSTOMER SERVICE AGENT

Sitel Barcelona - Oui.sncf | June 2019 - December 2019

- Provide world class customer service and support via e-mail, phone, chat and social media.
- $\bullet\,$ Make tickets for the claim department of refunds and complaints of customers
- Using exceptional people skills to get out in front of potential problems and proactively help customers

Evaluate customer and own experiences to create better upscaled strategies and service.

CUSTOMER SERVICE AGENT & SALES

Cygnific - KLM & De persgroep - Indebuurt | Nov 2018 - Juni 2019

- Deliver world class customer service and support
- Create tickets for customer claims, complaints and feedback/suggestions
- Evaluate and identify opportunities for process improvement
- Identify sales opportunities and create sale leads
- Pass on creative advise and tips on increasing revenue to B2B customers



LANGUAGES

• Dutch: Native

• English: Near Native

• Papiamento: Near Native

• Spanish: Intermediate

MARIËTTE EVERITZ

EXPERIENCES

SALES EXECUTIVE

De persgroep - Indebuurt | Feb 2019 - Juni 2019

- Deliver world class customer service and support
- Evaluate and identify opportunities for process improvement
- Identify sales opportunities and create sale leads
- Pass on creative advise and tips on increasing revenue to B2B customers Help companies increase in revenues and build customer loyalty.

OPERATION MANAGEMENT/MARKET RESEARCH

EF Education First (Corporate)| March 2018 - JuLy 2018 (Graduate/Thesis Intership)

- Give remote presentations and demonstrations to new users..
- Evaluate experiences and communications with users by creating and sending out surveys, analyze the data and make presentations for the empleyrs
- Analyse and create monthly reports of the progress of employees for the companies.
- Support the sales team by searching for new sale leads
- Complete administrative tasks in Salesforce for the sales team.

Creating a ready to implement Marketing Strategic plan on how to position a new B2B product in the Dutch market.

SALES AND RECRUITER/BUSINESS RESEARCH

Mr. Search/LER | Sept 2016 - Feb 2017 (Intership)

- Use the selection and improvement process and evluate the current process.
- Analyse and evaluate the desires and needs within the company (goals and mission)
- Create new strategies, implement and evaluate for the Strategy plan.
- Search for candidates per vacancy, contact them (interview the candidates and scan the resumes)
- Introduce the candidates to the companies and evaluate candidates with the company. Evaluate the internal business process and create a ready to use Process Strategy plan to improve the selection and recruitment process.

AMBASSADOR, MENTOR & CUSTOMER SERVICE AGENT

University of Applied Sciences | April 2015 - June 2018

- Provide the best customer service and support for (future) students, parents and teachers face-to-face and via e-mail.
- Give presentations and coaching at schools
- Evaluate experiences of and communications with future applicants by creating ideas for process improvement
- Help resolve any issue and/or doubts
- Planning activities for my colleagues for teambuilding and to pass on motivation and creativity in giving service.

Increased student application with 175% and decreased the number of dropouts/education change with 160%



WHO AM I

I am a strong believer in passing on knowledge, creativity and motivation. On a daily basis, I am making my surrounding crazy with being very positive and coming up with ideas how they can accomplish their dreams and desires.

My motto: 'Dare to dream, don't settle for less.'

I am always learning and like to identify trends. One of my missions is to travel around the world (or atleast 3/4 of it;)) and spread my positive motivation and believes that everyone can accomplish their dream. I like to be challenged, enjoy getting out of my comfy zone and learn/experience new things.

HOW TO CONTACT ME

Email: mariette.everitz@outlook.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/marietteeveritz

Skype: mariette_ve or mariette.everitz@outlook.com

MARIËTTE EVERITZ

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARTS: BUSINESS STUDIES, MAJOR IN ENTREPRENEURSHIP

University of Aplied Sciences Inholland | 2014 - 2018

MASTOR OF SCIENCE: MAJOR IN EDUCATION, TUTORING AND COACHING

IPA Aruba | 2007 - 2011

COLLEGE IN ECONOMICS: MAJOR IN FINANCE, ECONOMICS

EPI Economia Aruba | 2003 - 2007

COURSES

CERTIFIED ELITE PERFOMANCE COACHING (CERTIFICATE) (2022) SHECODES: WEB DEVELOPMENT (BASIC, PLUS REACT, RESPONSIVE (SEO)) (2021) CODE INSTITUTE 5-DAY CODING CHALLENGE (CERTIFICATE) (2021)

SPANISH (2007 / 2020 - ONGOING)
TRADING BY CONFLUENCE KINGS (2020)

MAIN INTERESTS

Volunteerwork: create activities/show and teach creative art classes with and for kids, youth & young adults

Sports: Dance, Diving, Fitness, Kickboxing, Hiking, Soccer Traveling: exploring & learning about different cultures

Web development: coding (websites/apps)

Coaching: Motivation in Life